justsomething.co 2015-09-05

# Privacy policy | Just something (creative)

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to [contact us](http://justsomething.co/contact/ "Contact us").

At justsomething.co, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by justsomething.co and how it is used.

##### Log Files

Like many other Web sites, justsomething.co makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

##### Cookies and Web Beacons

justsomething.co does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

##### DoubleClick DART Cookie

.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on justsomething.co.  
.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.justsomething.co and other sites on the Internet.  
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include Google Adsense.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on justsomething.co send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

justsomething.co has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. justsomething.co’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

##### Copyright

All images on justsomething.co are readily available in various places on the Internet and believed to be in public domain. Images posted are believed to be posted within our rights according to the U.S. Copyright Fair Use Act (title 17, U.S. Code.)

##### Claims of infringement

If you believe that any content appearing on justsomething.co infringes on your copyright, **[please let us know](http://justsomething.co/contact/ "Contact us")**.

justsomething.co claims no credit for any images featured on this site unless otherwise noted. All visual content is copyright to its respectful owners. If you own right to any of the images, and do not wish them to appear here, **[please let us know](http://justsomething.co/contact/ "Contact us")** and they will be promptly removed.

Email us the following informations and the infringing material will be removed as soon as possible.

(a) your name, address, telephone number, and e-mail address;  
(b) a description of the copyrighted work that you claim has been infringed;  
(c) the exact URL or a description of each place where alleged infringing material is located;  
(d) a statement by you that you have a good faith belief that the disputed use has not been authorized by you, your agent, or the law;  
(e) your electronic or physical signature or the electronic or physical signature of the person authorized to act on your behalf; and  
(f) a statement by you made under penalty of perjury, that the information in your notice is accurate, that you are the copyright owner or authorized to act on the copyright owner’s behalf

Please also note that under Section 512(f) of the Copyright Act any person who knowingly materially misrepresents that material or activity is infringing may be subject to liability.
